Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Negatives, Series 3; 10 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box (5.25 linear ft.)
  - Negative sheets 62-67, 68.1, 69-77, 78.1, 78.2, 1961-1962; black and white negatives: 35 mm: black and white prints: 3.5x5.5 in. (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets, 1944-1963; black and white transparency: 7x9.25 in. (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    Un-numbered
  - Negative sheets 79-91, 92.1, 92.2, 93-99, 1962-1963; black and white negatives: 35mm (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 3-5, 10, 100, 1945-1963; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x3.5 in.: black and white prints: 3.25x4.5 in. and 2.5x3.5 in. (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 101-115, 1963-1967; black and white negatives: 35mm (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 116-127, 1967-1971; black and white negatives: 35mm: black and white prints 3.5x5 in. (Oversize 1, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 128-132, 133.1, 133.2, 134.1-134.3, 135-137, 138.1, 138.2, 139.1-139.3, 1971-1973; black and white negatives: 35mm (Oversize 1, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 139.4-139.5, 140.1-140.7, 141.1-141.7, 1975-1978; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 141.8-141.9, 142.1-142.9, 143.1-143.6, 1979-1980; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 143.7-143.9, 144.1-144.4, 144.5A, 144.5B, 144.6-144.7, 144.8A, 144.8B, 144.9, 145.1-145.2, 1980 Sept -1982 Aug; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 145.3-145.9, 146.1-146.2, 147-154, 1982 Aug-1982 Dec; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 155-163, 164.1, 164.2, 165.1, 165.2, 166-169, 170.1, 1982 Dec-1983 Nov; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 170.2, 171-185, 1984 Jan-1984 Apr; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 186-200, 1984 Apr-1984 Jun; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in.: black and white transparacies: 3.5x4 in. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 201-216, 1984 Jun-1984 Sept; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 217-229, 1984 Sept-1984 Oct; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 230-248, 1984 Oct 11-1984 Oct 31; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 249-264, 1984 Nov 11-1984 Dec 12; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 265-281, 1984 Dec 18-1985 Jan 19; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Negative sheets 282-300, 1985 Jan 19-1985 Mar 11; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Negative sheets 301-318, 1985 Mar 16-1985 Mar 27; black and white negatives: 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 319- 337, 1985 Mar 27-1985 Apr 24; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 338-355, 1985 Mar 14-1985 May 12; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 356, 357.1-357.4, 358-373, 1985 May 14-1985 Jun 2; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 374-191, 1985 Jun 9-1985 July 6; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 392-400, 1985 July 7-1985 July 13; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 401-414, 1985 July 16-1985 July 29; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 415-431, 1985 July 29-1985 Aug 13; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 432-462, 1985 Aug 15-1985 Sept 27; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 463-500, 1985 Sept 29-1985 Nov 30; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 501-534, 1985 Dec 1-1986 Jan 31; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 535-565, 1986 Jan-1986 May 3; black and white negatives: 35mm and 2.5x2.5 in. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Negative sheets 566-600, 1986 May 10 - 1986 July 11; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Negative sheets 601 - 630, 1986 July 9 -1986 August 10; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 631 - 660, 1986 August 10 - 1986 October 11; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 661 - 682, 1986 August 14 - 1986 November 11; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 683 - 700, 1986 November 11 - 1986 December 21; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 701 - 730, 1986 December 21 - 1987 March 3; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 731 - 760, 1987 March 3 - 1987 April 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 761 - 780, 1987 April 19 - 1987 May 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 781 - 800, 1987 May 15 - 1987 June 13; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 801 - 830, 1987 June 14 - 1987 July 4; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 831 - 860, 1987 July 7 - 1987 August 1; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 861 - 880, 1987 July 28 - 1987 August 26; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 881 - 883, 884.1, 884.2, 885-900, 1987 September 2 - 1987 November 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Negative sheets 901 - 930, 1987 December 2 - 1988 January 19; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 931 - 960, 1988 January 18 - 1988 April 29; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 961 - 962; 979 - 1000, 1986 July - 1988 May 29; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 1001 - 1020, 1988 May 30 - 1988 July 9; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 1021 - 1050, 1988 July 9-10 - 1988 November 24 (?); black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 1051 - 1075, 1988 May 30 (?) - 1988 October 14; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 1077 - 1079; 1081 - 1100, 1988 October 15 - 1988 November 24 (?); black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 1101 - 1120, 1988 November 1 - 1988 December 4; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 1121 - 1140, 1988 December 4 - 1989 February 6; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 1141 - 1153.9, 1989 February 10 - 1989 April 30; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 1154.1 - 1154.6, 1989 May 3 - 1989 June 10; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 1171 - 1186.2, 1989 June 11 - 1989 June-July 20; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 1187 - 1200, 1989 July 19 - 1989 August 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 1201 - 1212; 1214 - 1215.2, 1989 August 19 - 1989 September 14; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 1217 - 1240.2, 1989 September 17 - 1989 November 2; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 1241 - 1245.3; 1246.1 - 1246.5, 1989 November 3 - 1989 November 23; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 1247 - 1252.4; 1253.1 - 1253.4; 1254 - 1256, 1989 November 30 - 1989 December 22; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 1257.1 - 1257.2; 1258 - 1275, 1989 December 23 - 1990 January 28; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 1276 - 1295; 1297 - 1300, 1990 January 29 - 1990 March 25; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 1301 - 1309.3; 1310 - 13.11, 1990 March 25 - 1990 April 10; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 1312 - 13.25; 13.26 - 1335, 1990 April 19 - 1990 June 4; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 1336 - 1353, 1990 June 15 - 1990 July 7; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 1354 - 1369, 1990 July 7 - 1990 July 22; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Negative sheets 1370 - 1376; 1378 - 1384, 1990 July 23 - 1990 August 25; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Negative sheets 1385 - 1400, 1990 August 26 - 1990 October 20; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Negative sheets 1401 - 1420, 1990 October 25 - 1990 December 2; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 1421 - 1440, 1990 December 2 - 1991 January 1; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 1441 - 1452.2; 1453 - 1460, 1991 January 1 - 1991 February 1-10; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 1461 - 1480, 1991 February 10 - 1991 March 23; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 1481 - 1500, 1991 March 23 - 1991 April 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 1501 - 1504; 1506 - 1520, 1991 February 15 - 1991 May 25; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 1521 - 1540, 1991 May 25 - 1991 May 29; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 1541.1-2; 1542 - 1560, 1991 May 29 - 1991 June 22; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 1561 - 1580, 1991 June 27 - 1991 July 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 1581 - 1600, 1991 July 15 - 1991 September 1; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 1601 - 1620, 1991 September 2 - 1991 October 21; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 1621 - 1640, 1991 October 21 - 1991 December 7; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Negative sheets 1641 - 1660, 1991 December 7 - 1992 February 1; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Negative sheets 1661 - 1680, 1992 February 5 - 1992 February 23; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Unnumbered negative sheets, 1991; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Negative sheets 1681 - 1700, 1992 March 23 - 1992 March 19; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 1701 - 1720, 1992 March 20 - 1992 April 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 1721 - 1740, 1992 April 22 - 1992 May 10; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 1741 - 1760, 1992 May 13 - 1992 June 6; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 1761.1 - 1761.3; 1762 - 1764.5, 1992 June 7 - 1992 August 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 1765 - 1785, 1992 June 16 - 1992 July 20; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 1786 - 1800, 1992 July 20 - 1992 May 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 1801 - 1820, 1992 August 19 - 1992 September 9; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 1821 - 1840, 1992 September 10 - 1992 October 28; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 1841 - 1842; 1843.1; 1843.2; 1844 - 1859; 1860.1; 1860.2; 1861 - 1870, 1992 October 28 - 1992 December 6; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 1871 - 1884; 1885.1; 1885.2; 1886 - 1900, 1992 December 6 - 1993 January 15; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 1901 - 1914; 1915.1; 1915.2; 1916 - 1918; 1920 - 1930, 1993 January 15 - 1993 February 22; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 1931 - 1953; 1954.1; 1954.2; 1955 - 1959, 1993 February 21 - 1993 May 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 1961 - 1963; 1966 - 1973; 1974.1; 1974.2; 1975 - 1980, 1993 May 28 - 1993 July 4; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 1982 - 1986; 1988 - 2000, 1993 July 9 - 1993 August 3; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 2002 - 2027; 2029 - 2030, 1993 August 7 - 1993 September 27; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 2031.1 - 2031.3; 2032 - 2062, 1993 September 28 - 1994 January 11; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 2063; 2064.1; 2064.2; 2065 - 2088; 2089.1; 2090 - 2093; 2095 - 3000, 1994 January 18 - 1994 June 4; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 2101 - 2106; 2108 - 2130, 1994 June 4 - 1994 September 8; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 2131 - 2160, 1994 September 10 - 1995 January 3; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Negative sheets 2163 - 2180, 1995 January 15 - 1995 February 27; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Negative sheets 2181 - 2196; 2198 - 2200, 1995 February 27 - 1995 April 8; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Negative sheets 2201 - 2202; 2204 - 2230, 1995 April 12 - 1995 June 21; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 2231 - 2260, 1995 June 23 - 1995 July 29; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 2261 - 2290, 1995 July 29 - 1995 September 20; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 2291.1; 2291.2; 2292 - 2298; 2299.2; 2300, 1995 September 20 - 1995 September 29; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 2301 - 2313; 2314.1; 2314.2; 2315 - 2324; 2326 - 2330, 1995 September 29 - 1995 December 1; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 2331 - 2360, 1995 December 1 - 1995 December 30; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Negative sheets 2361 - 2368; 2370 - 2390, 1996 January 1 - 1996 February 18; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Negative sheets 2391 - 2400, 1996 February 19 - 1996 March 2; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Negative sheets 2401 - 2430, 1996 March 2 - 1996 April 16; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Negative sheets 2431 - 2435; 2436.1; 2436.2; 2437 - 2460, 1996 April 13 - 1996 June 9; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Negative sheets 2461 - 2485, 1996 June 13 - 1996 August 5; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Negative sheets 2486 - 2500, 1996 August 5 - 1996 October 20; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Negative sheets 2501 - 2520, 1996 October 28 - 1997 January 26; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Negative sheets 2521 - 2533, 1997 February 3 - 1997 April 2; black and white negatives: 35mm (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dorfman, Elsa, circa 1997; negatives: various sizes (Item 12, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Brian, circa 1997; negatives: various sizes (Item 12, Folder 2)
- Series 4: Accession 2002-238, 2005-113: Ginsberg photographs
  - Miscellaneous photographs of Eastern teachers (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs by Trungpa (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Eastern teachers: photographs, cards, etc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Neal Cassidy, Burroughs, Kaufman, Ferlinghetti photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Richard Avedon photographs/proofs (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ginsberg: 1984, portrait with book, "Planet News" (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bob Dylan: negatives, proofs (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accession 2005-113: photograph reproductions of Kerouac, Orlovsky, Hunche, Burroughs (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Japanese Mural (Item 2, Folder 1)
  - Luanne Hansen (Item 2, Folder 2)
  - Proofs: Allen Ginsberg, Gary Snyder, Bob Dylan (Item 2, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Photocopies
  - Accession 2001-073: Photocopies (Box 1)
  - Accession 2001-073: Photocopies (Box 2)